hypothyroidmom.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Hypothyroid Mom

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Hypothyroid Mom LLC (“we”, “us”, “our”, “Company”) on the collection, use, share, protection, and disclosure of your information on the Company website (“Site”) and the services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively with the Site, the “Services”).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Site will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure, and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### 1\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION.

**User-provided information**

We collect, process, and use your information when you:

  * Register for our Services or sign in to an existing account including Company newsletter
  * Visit our website
  * Visit our social media platforms including Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Instagram, Google+ and YouTube
  * Connect to our Services using third-party accounts such as your email or social media
  * Contact us for support
  * Enter a sweepstakes, contest, promotion, survey, or poll

**Automatically collected information**

We and our service providers automatically collect certain information about you through:

  * Interaction with our Services
  * Cookies and other tracking technologies
  * Location-identifying technologies
  * Monitoring and analyzing trends, usage, and activities

The types of information you provide may include Personal Information. “Personal Information” means information that can be used to identify you (whether alone or in combination). The Personal Information you may provide to us may include:

  * First and last name
  * Email address
  * Mailing address
  * Phone number
  * Payment information (such as payment account name, payment account number, payment card expiration date, and billing address)

We may also collect Personal Information and other information based on your use of the Services:

  * The nature of the product or service requested or purchased
  * How you connect to our Services, such as your IP address, unique device identifiers, device or session IDs, and information regarding the network and connected hardware (e.g., computer or mobile device)
  * Browsing, shopping, and purchase history
  * Your geolocation
  * Click-stream data (the page-by-page paths you take as you browse through our Services)

#### 2\. USE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT. WE MAY USE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU IN THE FOLLOWING WAYS.

**Manage Your Account**

If you provide us with Personal Information, we may use it to: (i) process your registration with our Services, including verifying whether your email address is active and valid and enrolling you into our programs; (ii) monitor and manage your account; (iii) track your shopping, deliver you any rewards or payments, and identify opportunities for rewards and/or offers; (iv) send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and administrative messages; (v) provide you customer service regarding your account and reply to your questions, comments and requests; (vi) comply with legal and regulatory provisions; (vii) assess risk and prevent fraud, and (viii) send relevant content, resources, products, and services.

**Improve Our Services**

We may process information through analyzing and monitoring usages and trends and performing statistical analyses to improve our Services and the websites, applications, marketing efforts, and the products and services of our affiliates to provide a better service to you in the future. We may also use this information to adapt Service content to be more likely to be of interest to you.

**Provide You Marketing Information**

To provide you more personalized offers and/or special offers, discounts and similar information, Hypothyroid Mom may send you newsletters, rewards, discounts, promotion codes, events, and general information about the Service.

**Administer Contests, Sweepstakes, and Promotions**

From time to time, Company may invite you to enter various contests, sweepstakes, surveys or promotions. If you choose to participate in a contest or promotion, your Personal Information may be used to administer the contest, such as to determine your eligibility for the contest, to award a prize, or to deliver the prize.

#### 3\. SHARING OF INFORMATION.

We may share the information we collect, including your Personal Information, with third parties under the following circumstances.

**Service Providers and Business Partners**

We do not sell your Personal Information and only share it with third parties to operate our Services. We may share your Personal Information with our service providers that perform marketing services and other business operations on our behalf. For example, we may partner with other companies to provide you support services, authentication services, prevent fraud on our Services, administer our promotions, referral programs, sweepstakes, and surveys, perform analytics, maintain the accuracy of our databases, fulfill your product purchases, and administer your rewards or payments.

**Affiliates, Sponsors, Partners, and Resources**

We participate in affiliate, sponsor, and partner marketing. We include affiliate links to relevant resources, events, products, and services. This means that we may earn a commission when you click on or make purchases via affiliate links. Our affiliates, sponsors, and partners may elect to provide a discount code with link to products or services. We also regularly include links to websites and social media platforms that include helpful information and resources including published scientific studies and health information. Once you click on any link and exit Company Site or Company social media platform, your visit to the new website, web page, or social media platform is subject to the privacy policy held by that partner, sponsor, affiliate, or resource. If you elect to purchase a product, service, or event on the website of an affiliate, sponsor, partner or resource, your purchase is subject to the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

**Guest Writers**

We include guest posts by guest writers to provide valuable information to our readers. The content they provide in their articles at Company website is their own. When you exit Company website to visit their website, social media platforms or recommended resources, your visit is subject to the privacy policy held by the owners of those websites or social media platforms. Company in some cases will partner with guest writer in an affiliate, sponsor, or partner relationship and an affiliate link or link with discount code will be included in the guest article. Once you click on said links and exit Company, your visit is subject to the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting.

**Protection of Rights and Other Legal Purposes**

We may share the information we collect, including Personal Information, to the extent permitted by applicable law, (i) in response to subpoenas or other legal process or if in our good faith opinion such disclosure is required or permitted by law; (ii) at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, including, but not limited to, meeting law enforcement requirements; (iii) to defend our terms and conditions or other policies applicable to our Services; and (iv) to protect the rights, property, life, health, security and safety of us or any third party.

**Business Transfers**

We may share the information we collect, including Personal Information, with any third party in connection with, or during negotiations of, any proposed or actual merger, purchase, sale (including a liquidation, realization, foreclosure, or repossession), or any other type of acquisition of all or any portion of Company assets, conveyance or transfer of all or a portion of our business to another company.

#### 4\. YOUR CHOICES.

You can use many of the features of the Services without registering, thereby limiting the type of information that we collect. You can always opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of some of our features. Even when you elect to subscribe to the Site newsletter, you may at any time change your preferences, unsubscribe or opt out of receiving marketing emails from us by using the unsubscribe link or update subscription preferences link in the footer of every marketing email or by emailing us at contact@hypothyroidmom.com. Upon written request, we will provide you with information on whether we hold any Personal Information.

#### 5\. PROMOTIONAL COMMUNICATIONS.

By signing up for Company newsletter, you may receive periodic emails from Company. You can opt out of receiving such communications from us at any time by (i) clicking on the Unsubscribe link in the footer of every email; (ii) updating your subscription preferences in the footer of every email; or (iii) contacting us contact@hypothyroidmom.com.

#### 6\. COOKIES, WEB BEACONS OR SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES

We and our partners may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We use cookies for many purposes, including, without limitation, authentication, tracking user preferences or web pages visited while using our Services. Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. If you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on the Service. This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer.

#### 7\. GOOGLE ANALYTICS, TARGETING, TRACKING.

We, and third parties with which we partner, may also use cookies, pixels, and other technologies to automatically collect information about your use of the Services, such as your click-stream data, browsing history, IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked, and conversion information. Data collected from a particular browser or device may be used with another computer or device that is linked to the browser or device on which such data was collected (also known as cross-linking). Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies. Third parties are responsible for their use of cookies.

#### 8\. THIRD PARTY DATA.

The Services contain hyperlinks to websites of merchants and retailers and other websites or locations that we do not control and are operated and controlled by third parties (“Third Party Websites”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through the Service or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

#### 9\. SOCIAL FEATURES.

Certain functionalities on the Services are specifically designed to permit interactions that you initiate between the Services and third-party websites or services, including third-party social networks (“Social Features”). Examples of Social Features include features that enable you to transmit your account content from a third-party website or service to our Services; to “like” or “share” our Services’ content on other websites or services; to sign in to the Services using your username and password from a third-party site or service; and to connect our Services with a third-party website or service. If you choose to use Social Features, the information you post or provide access to may be used by us and/or publicly displayed on our Services or by the provider of the Social Feature that you use. Similarly, if you post information on a third-party platform that references our Services (e.g., by using a hashtag associated with Company in a tweet or status update), your post may be published on our Services in accordance with the terms of the third-party website or service. When you use our Services with a third-party site or service, both Company and the third party may have access to certain information about you and your use of our Services and the third-party site or service. The information we collect in connection with Social Features is subject to this Privacy Policy. The information collected and stored by the third parties remains subject to those third parties’ privacy policies, including whether the third parties continue to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on those third party websites or services.

#### 10\. USER CONTENT.

Some of your activity on and through the Services is public by default. This may include, but is not limited to, content you have posted publicly on the Site or otherwise through the Services, such as comments you make on the Site or on social media platforms or other submissions by you to the Site. Please also remember that if you choose to provide Personal Information using certain public features of the Services, then that information may be publicly available. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or information that you submit through the Services. When commenting on Site, we encourage you to not use your full name.

#### 11\. PARENTAL PERMISSION.

This Site is not intended for use by children under 18 years of age. We do not knowingly permit children under age 18 to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas.

#### 12\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY.

This Privacy Policy is current as of the date set forth above. Company reserves the right to change this privacy policy from time to time consistent with applicable privacy laws and principles. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this Privacy Policy. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

#### 13\. CONTACT US.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email at contact@hypothyroidmom.com with Subject: Privacy Policy.
